Melville S. Munro Papers MS036
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Loose prints, 1890 -- 1959; MS036.011; 0.75 Linear Feet; 403 Digital Object(s)
  - Glee Club Officers, 1930-03-07; MS036.011.DO.00581; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
    Student activities; photographic print; Glee Club
  - Tufts Glee Club 1931-1932, October, MS036.011.DO.00582; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
  - Glee Club, 1937 -- 1938; MS036.011.DO.00595; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
  - Delta Tau Delta Construction, 1936-07-22; MS036.011.DO.00599; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
    75
    Buildings; Greek letter societies; Housing; photographic print; Delta Tau Delta
  - Delta Tau Delta New Student Study, 1936-11-06; MS036.011.DO.00600; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
    Greek letter societies; Buildings; Housing; photographic print; Delta Tau Delta
  - Miner Hall (Front), 1928-05-31; MS036.011.DO.00603; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
    Buildings; Administrative; Academic; photographic print; Crane Theological School; Divinity School; School of Religion
  - Zeta Psi Renovated House, 1940; MS036.011.DO.00605; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
    Buildings; Housing; Greek letter societies; photographic print; Zeta Psi
  - Delta Tau Delta Squash Team Champions - Inter-fraternity, 1940-03-22; MS036.011.DO.00606; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
    Greek letter societies; Athletics; Squash; photographic print; Hosmer, Humphrey B.; Kinnison; Miller, Brewster S.; Baylies, Wallace B.; Milhench, Arthur L.; Linden, Henry; Delta Tau Delta
  - New Delta Tau Delta House Sleeping Room, 1936-11-06; MS036.011.DO.00607; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
  - Delta Tau Delta New Lounge, 1936-11-06; MS036.011.DO.00608; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
  - Delta Tau Delta Dance Decorations, 1939-12-08; MS036.011.DO.00609; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
    Greek letter societies; photographic print; Delta Tau Delta
  - Delta Tau Delta Group, 1936-11-06; MS036.011.DO.00610; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
  - New Delta Tau Delta House Lounge showing Library, 1936-11-06; MS036.011.DO.00611; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 52)
  - Mural seen as one approaches the library from the living room in new fraternity house of Delta Upsilon, MS036.011.DO.00619; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 89)
  - One of the Class Rooms - Goddard Hall, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00642; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 53)
    Buildings; Academic; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Entrance to Goddard Hall, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00643; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 53)
  - Fletcher School Auditorium - Goddard Hall, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00644; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 53)
  - East wing of Wilson House, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00645; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 53)
    Buildings; Housing; Dormitories; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Sketch of Wilson House, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00651; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 53)
  - Dramatics at Jackson Gym [interior], 1914; MS036.011.DO.00659; Munro, Melville S.; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 93)
    Student activities; People; photographic print
  - Tufts Football Team, 1924; MS036.011.DO.00688; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 54)
    Athletics; People; Football; photographic print
  - [Jamming], 1919; MS036.011.DO.00698; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
  - 1918-1919 Gate Night, MS036.011.DO.00699; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
  - [Jamming], 1919; MS036.011.DO.00700; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
  - Cap Rush, 1919; MS036.011.DO.00701; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
  - Tufts 7 - Yale 3 baseball bonfire, 1919; MS036.011.DO.00706; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
  - Freshman, 1920; MS036.011.DO.00710; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
    People; Academic; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.
  - Sophmores, 1920; MS036.011.DO.00711; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
    People; Academic; photographic print
  - Blue Duckling Banquet on campus, 1915; MS036.011.DO.00712; Munro, Melville S.; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 93)
  - College Sing at gym, 1915; MS036.011.DO.00713; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
  - Blue Duckling feast, 1914; MS036.011.DO.00719; Munro, Melville S.; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 93)
  - Pre-registration Freshmen coming out of chapel - North entrance - showing branches from trees - wind storm debris, 1938-09-22; MS036.011.DO.00721; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
    People; Academic; Buildings; Chapels; photographic print
  - Jam, 1916; MS036.011.DO.00725; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
    Date is approximate; 5.5 x 4
  - Jam, 1916; MS036.011.DO.00726; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
  - Jam, 1916; MS036.011.DO.00732; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
  - Just before the rope breaks - A Sophomore - Freshman Tug of War, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00772; Munro, Melville S.
    People; Students
  - Jumbo Snow Sculpture, Alpha Kappa Pi, 1939-03-14; MS036.011.DO.00776; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 94)
    Greek letter societies; photographic print; Alpha Kappa Pi
  - Lincoln Memorial Snow Sculpture Delta Tau Delta, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00780; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 94)
  - Snow Girl - Front - Zeta Psi, 1939-03-14; MS036.011.DO.00781; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 94)
    Greek letter societies; photographic print; Zeta Psi
  - Flag Pole - Getting Ready to Paint, MS036.011.DO.00782; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
    no date
  - H.O. Bishop (P.T. Barnum look-alike) and Tufts President Leonard Carmichael with Jumbo, MS036.011.DO.00785; Munro, Melville S.
    People; Carmichael, Leonard; Bishop, H. O.; Jumbo
  - In mineralogy lab, MS036.011.DO.00810; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 93)
    no date; 4 x 6 print
    photographic print; Jackson College
  - Chapel tower through Alumni Gate, 1929-06-16; MS036.011.DO.00817; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 95)
    5x7 mounted 8x10
    Gates; photographic print
  - Starkweather Gate and Miner Hall, 1930-06-14; MS036.011.DO.00818; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 95)
    5x8 mounted 8x10
  - Dearborn Gate in snow, 1929-01-15; MS036.011.DO.00825; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 95)
  - Building bleachers, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00840; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
  - Horribles, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00841; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
    Events; photographic print
  - Horribles, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00842; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
  - Horribles, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00843; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
  - Capen House and Professors Row, MS036.011.DO.00844; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
    Buildings; Housing; Dormitories; photographic print
  - Robinson Hall and Hodgdon Gate, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00851; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 97)
  - Goddard Hall and Bowen Gate, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00852; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 97)
  - Dramatics, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00863; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
    Theater; Student activities; photographic print
  - Production of "Minuet", November, 1934; MS036.011.DO.00864; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 97)
  - Robbery Scene in Dramatic Production, 1920; MS036.011.DO.00865; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 97)
  - Production of "Madame Butterfly", 1940; MS036.011.DO.00866; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 97)
  - Actress in "Madame Butterfly", 1940; MS036.011.DO.00867; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 97)
  - Dramatic Production, 1940; MS036.011.DO.00868; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 98)
  - Production of "Guard Thy Virginity", 1929 -- 1930; MS036.011.DO.00869; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 98)
    Production associated with Department of Nursing
  - Dramatic Production, 1940; MS036.011.DO.00870; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 98)
  - Dramatic Production, 1940; MS036.011.DO.00871; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 98)
  - Chemistry Lecture Hall in Curtis Hall, 1917-03-29; MS036.011.DO.00876; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
  - Curtis Hall, Boston and College Avenues, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00877; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 98)
  - Curtis Hall from Memorial Steps, 1937-10-15; MS036.011.DO.00880; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
  - Dramatics, MS036.011.DO.00890; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
    No date
    photographic print; Pen, Paint, and Pretzels
  - Dramatics, MS036.011.DO.00891; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
  - Production of Emperor Jones, December, 1928; MS036.011.DO.00892; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
    Not found in box, 10/03/2022.
    Theater; Student activities; Students; photographic print
  - Production of "Counselor at Law," August 24-25, 1935; MS036.011.DO.00893; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
  - The New Infirmary at Tufts Dental School, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00894; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
    photographic print; School of Dental Medicine
  - Faculty in costume to greet medical freshmen, November, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00899; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 99)
    Each person respresents doctor of a special period in costume of the day, at faculty reception to medical freshmen.
    People; Faculty; photographic print; School of Medicine
  - Dramatics, 1920; MS036.011.DO.00900; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
  - Working with modern drill at dental school, 1933-11-16; MS036.011.DO.00901; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
    Students; Dental students; photographic print; School of Dental Medicine
  - Backstage at switchboard, 1933-12-06; MS036.011.DO.00902; Unknown (Box Shared 96)
  - Actress in costume, 1930-02-02; MS036.011.DO.00903; Unknown (Box Shared 96)
  - Cast of "Rose and Ring", 1928-02-27; MS036.011.DO.00904; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 96)
  - Jumbo mascot at sporting event, 1920; MS036.011.DO.00943; Unknown (Box Shared 100)
    Students; photographic print; Jumbo
  - Cousens operating shovel at Gym construction site, 1931; MS036.011.DO.00960; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 100)
    Prexy feels the job is well started and turns the shovel over to the regular operator. #9413
    Buildings; Physical Plant; photographic print; Cousens, John Albert
  - Construction of Counsens Gymnasium, 1931; MS036.011.DO.00962; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 100)
    Front entrance of new gymnasium. #9562
    Buildings; Athletics; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.
  - Homecoming football game, 1939; MS036.011.DO.00963; Unknown (Box Shared 100)
  - Construction of Fletcher Hall, 1926; MS036.011.DO.00969; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 100)
    President Cousens's Alumni Card Club, M.S. Munro collection
    Buildings; Dormitories; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.
  - Officers of All Around Club, 1938; MS036.011.DO.00974; Unknown (Box Shared 100)
    Student activities; photographic print; All Around Club; Jackson College
  - Fletcher Hall, 1920; MS036.011.DO.00982; Unknown (Box Shared 100)
  - Eugene Bucklin Bowen at dedication of Bowen Porch, 1939-10-28; MS036.011.DO.00983; Unknown (Box Shared 100)
    Buildings; People; photographic print; Bowen, Eugene B.
  - Dedication ceremony of Bowen Porch, 1939-10-28; MS036.011.DO.00984; Unknown (Box Shared 100)
    People; Buildings; College presidents; photographic print; Carmichael, Leonard
  - The original Jumbo displayed in Barnum Hall, 1940; MS036.011.DO.00985; Unknown (Box Shared 100)
    Buildings; Academic; photographic print; Jumbo
  - Eaton Library, 1931-06-06; MS036.011.DO.00987; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 101)
    8x10
    Buildings; Academic; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.
  - Walk on Professors Row, 1930; MS036.011.DO.00994; Unknown (Box Shared 100)
  - Hurricane damage to Ballou Hall, 1938; MS036.011.DO.01000; Unknown (Box Shared 101)
  - Mayoralty Campaign in Jackson College, 1938-05-05; MS036.011.DO.01013; Unknown (Box Shared 100)
    Students; People; Events; Mayoralty; photographic print; Jackson College
  - The Jam, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01019; Unknown (Box Shared 100)
    Students; Events; Jam; photographic print
  - Boxing in gym class, 1940; MS036.011.DO.01022; Unknown (Box Shared 101)
    Date is approximate; 8x10
    Students; Athletics; Boxing; People; photographic print
  - Brenda and R. Robinson, 1940-09-17; MS036.011.DO.01023; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
    Students; People; photographic print; Robinson, Brenda; Robinson, R.
  - Metcalf Hall from Professor Munro's window, 1937-04-12; MS036.011.DO.01027; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 102)
  - Construction of Metcalf Hall West through Dearborn Gate, 1937-04-28; MS036.011.DO.01028; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
  - Metcalf Hall, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01029; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
    Buildings; Housing; Dormitories; photographic print; Jackson College; Coll. of Liberal Arts & Jackson College
  - Construction of Memorial Steps, 1929-05-01; MS036.011.DO.01051; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 102)
  - Lewis Manly, 1945; MS036.011.DO.01061; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 102)
    Faculty; photographic print; Manly, Lewis Frederick
  - Bowen Porch, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01065; Unknown (Box Shared 103)
  - Goddard Chapel, 1935; MS036.011.DO.01072; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
  - Goddard Chapel, 1922; MS036.011.DO.01078; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
    2.5x5
  - Goddard Chapel Tower, 1940; MS036.011.DO.01080; Unknown (Box Shared 104)
  - Goddard Chapel sanctuary, MS036.011.DO.01082; Unknown (Box Shared 104)
    No date; 8x10
  - Goddard Chapel, 1929; MS036.011.DO.01083; Unknown (Box Shared 104)
  - Goddard Chapel at night, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01086; Milne, George D. (Box Shared 104)
  - Service flag in Goddard Chapel, April, 1919; MS036.011.DO.01088; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
  - Jackson athletics - archery, 1940; MS036.011.DO.01095; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
    Athletics; Archery; Students; People; photographic print; Jackson College
  - Jackson College hayride, 1945; MS036.011.DO.01096; Unknown (Box Shared 105)
    Students; People; photographic print; Jackson College
  - Dissection of rats, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01101; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Lambert, Fred D.; Coll. of Liberal Arts & Jackson College; Dept. of Biology
  - Dissection of cat at Tufts Medical School, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01102; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
  - Construction of Tufts golf course, 1924; MS036.011.DO.01107; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
  - Crane Theological Faculty, 1935; MS036.011.DO.01113; Unknown (Box Shared 105)
    Faculty; People; photographic print; Crane Theological School; School of Religion
  - Tufts College Band, 1937; MS036.011.DO.01119; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 105)
    Student activities; photographic print; Tufts College Band
  - Student solving an equation, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01120; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 105)
  - Crowell-Neal wedding at Goddard Chapel, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01121; Unknown (Box Shared 105)
  - Jackson College "Frosh" rules, 1932; MS036.011.DO.01122; Unknown (Box Shared 105)
  - Class Day, 1926; MS036.011.DO.01123; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
  - Horribles parade, Junior Day, 1926; MS036.011.DO.01125; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
  - Class of 1926, 10 year reunion, 1936; MS036.011.DO.01126; Unknown (Box Shared 106)
    Alumni and alumnae; photographic print
  - Class of 1926, 10 year anniversary, 1936; MS036.011.DO.01127; Unknown (Box Shared 106)
  - Mr. Bowen presents lions, Alumni Day, 1922 -- 1923; MS036.011.DO.01128; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
    Events; photographic print; Bowen, Eugene B.
  - Prof. Andrew's Czechoslavakians, 1923; MS036.011.DO.01131; Unknown (Box Shared 106)
  - Unidentified faculty member, MS036.011.DO.01133; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
  - Professor Gilmer, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01134; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
    Faculty; photographic print; Gilmer, Professor
  - Professor Neal Cat, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01135; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
    Faculty; photographic print; Cat, Neal
  - Professor Leo Lewis, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01136; Unknown (Box Shared 102)
    Faculty; photographic print; Lewis, Leo R.
  - Jackson College freshmen, 1915; MS036.011.DO.01137; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 102)
    Students; People; Women; photographic print; Jackson College
  - Class of 1918 marching in Class Day parade, 1928; MS036.011.DO.01138; Unknown (Box Shared 106)
  - Original bell of Bowen chimes dedicated in 1926 on Alumni Day, MS036.011.DO.01144; Unknown (Box Shared 106)
  - Jackson "frosh" bows, 1940-10-03; MS036.011.DO.01147; Unknown (Box Shared 106)
    Jean Blum, Jean Campbell
    Students; photographic print; Campbell, Jean; Blum, Jean; Jackson College
  - Class Day Committee, 1938-05-16; MS036.011.DO.01150; Unknown (Box Shared 106)
  - Cheerleaders, 1935-09-26; MS036.011.DO.01180; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    Student activities; People; Students; photographic print; Cheerleading
  - Coach Dussault and two hurdlers, 1939-01-08; MS036.011.DO.01182; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    Eddie Dugger on left
    Athletics; Track (Men's); People; photographic print; Dugger, Edward; Dussault, Ding
  - Track team, 1935-05-15; MS036.011.DO.01185; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    Athletics; Track (Men's); Students; People; photographic print
  - Tufts medical amphitheater, Huntington Ave. School, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01186; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    photographic print; School of Medicine
  - Dr. Reis and Dr. Haskins in the chemistry lab, 1927-12-15; MS036.011.DO.01187; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    Dr. Reis, Dr. Haskins
    Faculty; People; photographic print; Dept. of Chemistry
  - Dr. Timothy Leary, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01188; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 107)
    Faculty; People; photographic print; Leary, Dr. Timothy; School of Medicine
  - Dr. Leary teaches pathology in ampitheatre at City Hospital, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01189; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 107)
  - Medical school building, 1927-12-09; MS036.011.DO.01190; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    Buildings; photographic print; School of Medicine
  - Tufts letter carrier Ole Mortensen, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01195; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    People; photographic print; Mortenson, Ole
  - Tufts mail carrier Ole Mortensen, 1959; MS036.011.DO.01196; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    People; photographic print; Mortensen, Ole
  - Tufts faculty, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01198; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    back row: Mr. Averill (treasury), Professor Reed (German), Dean Wren, Professor Conner, Professor Chase, front row: Professor Lewis, Professor Durkee, Miss Ethel Hayes, Miss Blanche Hooper, Mrs. Nellie Reynolds, Dean Rollins, Professor Dennison, Professor Munro, Professor Ransom
    Faculty; People; College administrators; photographic print; Averill, Harvey E.; Reed, William H.; Wren, Frank G.; Connor, Samuel; Chase, Charles; Lewis, Leo R.; Durkee, Frank W; Hayes, Ethel M.; Hooper, Blanche; Reynolds, Nellie; Rollins, Edwin B.; Denison, William K.; Munro, Melville S.; Ransom, John C.; Faculty of Arts and Sciences
  - Three deans of Tufts University, 1928-01-21; MS036.011.DO.01199; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    Dean Rollins (English), Dean Wren (Liberal Arts), Dean Bush (Jackson)
    Faculty; photographic print; Rollins, Edwin B.; Wren, Frank G.; Bush, Edith L.; Faculty of Arts and Sciences
  - Betty Davis in the Publications Office, 1930-12-09; MS036.011.DO.01202; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    Betty Davis
    People; photographic print; Davis, Betty; Office of Publications
  - Janitor William Ashman at furnace in chemical lab, 1939-04-28; MS036.011.DO.01203; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    People; photographic print; Ashman, William
  - Tufts janitor William Ashman, 1939-04-28; MS036.011.DO.01204; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    William Ashman
  - Tufts College Band, 1933-11-11; MS036.011.DO.01208; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
  - Orchestra - D.U. House, 1931-06-01; MS036.011.DO.01209; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
  - Men doing laundry during World War I, 1918; MS036.011.DO.01229; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 109)
    World War, 1914-1918; People; Students; photographic print; Student Army Training Corps
  - Auto Laboratory during World War I, 1918; MS036.011.DO.01230; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 109)
    World War, 1914-1918; Students; People; Automobiles; photographic print
  - Men in military uniforms, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01231; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 109)
    Dates are approximate; 8x10
  - Eleanor Josselyn in green house, 1914-01-13; MS036.011.DO.01232; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    Students; photographic print; Josselyn, Eleanor H.
  - Emily Bettencourt in biology with model of human skull, 1937-11-19; MS036.011.DO.01235; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
    Students; photographic print; Bettencourt, Emily
  - Dorothy Myers at telescope in astronomy, 1930-02-18; MS036.011.DO.01236; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
    Students; photographic print; Myers, Dorothy
  - Mayoralty campaign candidate, Shirley Boulanger, 1940-05-15; MS036.011.DO.01247; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    Mayoralty; Events; Students; People; photographic print; Boulanger, Shirley
  - Tufts Orchestra, 1934-02-21; MS036.011.DO.01249; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 109)
    Student activities; Music and musical performances; Students; People; photographic print
  - String quartet, 1932-03-14; MS036.011.DO.01250; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    Student activities; Students; People; Music and musical performances; photographic print
  - President John Albert Cousens, 1936-03-28; MS036.011.DO.01263; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 108)
    photo copy of painting of President John Albert Cousens
    People; College presidents; photographic print; Cousens, John Albert
  - Student experiementing in science lab, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01266; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    Academic; photographic print
  - Students working with survey equipment, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01270; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
  - Pot furnace work at chemical lab, 1934-11-28; MS036.011.DO.01271; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
  - Frunace work at chemical lab, 1936-03-26; MS036.011.DO.01272; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
  - Passing of ceremonial mace at inauguration of President Leonard Carmichael, 1938-11-14; MS036.011.DO.01277; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 57)
    Faculty; photographic print; Carmichael, Leonard
  - President John A. Cousens with Jumbo's elephant ankus, January, 1923; MS036.011.DO.01288; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Cousens, John Albert
  - President John A. Cousens with John Holmes, 1936-03-06; MS036.011.DO.01289; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Cousens, John Albert; Holmes, John
  - President John A. Cousens, 1928; MS036.011.DO.01290; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 57)
    President John A. Cousens
  - Theta Delta Chi fraternity house, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01330; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 58)
    Buildings; photographic print; Theta Chi
  - Broadcasting faculty group, 1922-03-23; MS036.011.DO.01332; Unknown (Box Shared 58)
  - Radio station, 1935-10-31; MS036.011.DO.01335; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 58)
  - Campus Radio Station, 1935-10-31; MS036.011.DO.01336; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 58)
  - Professor Wheeler and the language recorder, 1938-04-13; MS036.011.DO.01346; Unknown (Box Shared 58)
    Professor Wheeler
    Faculty; People; Students; photographic print
  - Psychology deception test, 1930-03-11; MS036.011.DO.01347; Unknown (Box Shared 58)
    Academic; Students; People; photographic print; Dept. of Psychology
  - Athlete throwing the shot-put, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01353; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
  - Jam, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01369; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
    Student activities; Jam; photographic print
  - Student tug-of-war, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01370; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
    Date is approximate; 2.5 x 5
  - Commencement at Memorial Steps, 1935; MS036.011.DO.01383; Munro, Melville S. (Box 18)
    In Memories: To an Alumnus, UA036/003-018#006 p. 6.
    Commencement; People; photographic print
  - Melville S. Munro, 1904; MS036.011.DO.01437; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 60)
    Faculty; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.
  - Tufts College railroad station, 1914; MS036.011.DO.01439; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 60)
    Railroad stations; photographic print